<?xml version='1.0'  encoding='ISO-8859-1'?><?xml-stylesheet title='XSL_formatting' type='text/xsl' href='//css/rss.xsl'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:GetJealous="http://www.GetJealous.com" ><channel>
<copyright>2002-2005 (c) GetJealous.com, All rights reserved.</copyright>
<GetJealous:self_url>http://www.getjealous.com/dion/rss.xml</GetJealous:self_url>

<title>Dion and Duane</title>
<description></description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/dion</link>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=407904&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>The last Hurrah</title>
<description>So, we&#39;re back and have been for some time, but I guess that now I&#39;m at work with nothing to do it would be time to finish this wonderful epic that has been our trip. After Chicago it was time to increase our carbon footprint just that little bit more with a flight to Boston.  The home of the Boston tea party and the basis for the American war of Independence.  If you are a proud Brit who doesn&#39;t ...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=407904&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=394637&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>My kind of town, Chicago is</title>
<description>Touchdown at Chicago&#39;s O&#39;Hare airport and we aree given another public transport system to negotiate.  Fortunately, due to track repair works that put Englands to shame, crossing Chicago takes a good 3 hours. Eventually we find ourselves in the Loyolla universtiy part of the city.  Tierd and unable to drink in our hostel we fall into a local bar.  Being surrounded by drunk students all pretending ...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=394637&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=393559&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>Road Trip: we've been having fun, driving in the sun.</title>
<description>In the words of Gemma and Alison:  &#34;So with &#39;Hotel California&#39; blasting out of the stereo we took to the road to travel the famous Highway 1 coastal route bound for San Diego.  With stops in Santa Cruz, Cambria, and even &#39;The OC&#39; itself - Newport Beach - we had an amazing few days and a great start to our &#39;extended adventure.&#39; [unable to say goodbye the girls had to extend their trip by two weeks]...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=393559&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 7 Sep 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=385240&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>.........flowers in your hair!!</title>
<description>After enough of the manufactured, beautiful people vibe of LA we headed off to Sna Francisco upon our air-conditioned shuttle bus provided by the hostel.  The only issue was that the air-con hadn&#39;t been turned on - you have no idea how hot it was.  India and SE Asia were not a patch on it.

So, finally, we arrived in Frisco and immediately had a good feel for the place.  More grubby and down to ...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=385240&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 3 Sep 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=390223&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>Sweet dreams my LAX</title>
<description>Change of country, time zone and date.  Que the longest day ever which caused Thursday to run for 42 hours.  There seemed only one way to cope with such a body shattering experience and that was to invoke international jet-lag laws and have a drink (well before the 4 o&#39;clock watershed!)  With ourselves in a very American British pub we staring putting away the Guinness and then wandered along Sant...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=390223&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=380018&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>The end days!</title>
<description>With time in NZ drawing to a close it was time to assess what there was left to do.  One more LOTR film and an epic voyage from Wellington to Christchurch.  So we stumbled onto Upper Hutt - described as the dormitory of Wellington - and were put up by Tabitha and Chris.  While they went off to school we became aquainted with Upper Hutt (it didn&#39;t take long) and NZ TV.  With Duane&#39;s replacement pas...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=380018&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=390222&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>The North Island.</title>
<description>From Wellington we drove to Taumatawhakatanginangakoavavotamateaturipukakapikimaungahoronukupokaiwhenvakitanatahu which claims to have the logest name in the world (ousting the train station in Whales) and I believe it does however the only thing here is a sign in a layby giving its name and a hill in the distance and obviously a couple of sheep. So we drove on and spent the night in Napier a town...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=390222&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=378165&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>North - West - North - East - North</title>
<description>With the all action, adrenaline capital of the world safely behind us we set out to explore the temperate rainforest and glacier covered West coast of NZ.  An epic drive across snow covered mountains to the sea took us within spitting distance of the Franz Josef glacier (so named because it looks like Austro-Hungarian leaders beard) and so we put on our crampons and headed up the icey face.  Spect...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=378165&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=380019&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>Ski School; On the Piste (apologies for the pun).</title>
<description>Well we arrived back in Queenstown and sat aroung in our shorts while we washed all our clothes - this illustrating the down side of living out of a van - and an early night was called for since the bell was sent for 06:30. The bus picked us up the next morning at 07:30 and we headed up to The Remarkables. Kitted out we headed of to our first lesson I opted for the ab initio class and Dion headed ...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=380019&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=372904&#38;go=dion</guid>
<title>The South of the South</title>
<description>We headed out from Christchurch full of petrol and raring to go, with dreams and aspirations of climbing the infamous Mount Cook and taking in the sights and beauty of as many of the LOTR locations that we could possibly find.  With time on our side, we parked up in Lake Tekapo, tried to cook a meal on a camping stove and tested out the camper van...........woke up a little sore, but i&#39;m sure it j...</description>
<link>http://www.getjealous.com/getjealous.php?action=showdiaryentry&#38;diary_id=372904&#38;go=dion</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 7 Aug 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
